

CONTACT INFO



Cluj-Napoca, Romania



0761341586



bm.bogdanmuntean@gmail.com



https://bogdan-muntean.github.io/

LANGUAGE

Romanian: Native

English: Upper-independent

German: Beginner Spanish: Beginner

HARD SKILLS

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, GitHub, Git, Linux Responsive Web Dev C, C++, Data structures Algorithms, Computer Science, Research Digital native

SOFT SKILLS

Adaptability, Responsibility Time management, Organization Collaboration, Flexibility Emotional intelligence, Teamwork Interpersonal skills, Listening Writing skills, Management Public speaking, Persuasion Presentation, Motivating Multitasking, Innovation Logical thinking, Initiative Problem solving, Patience

MORE ABOUT ME



Visit my online CV by scanning the QR code to learn more about me.

Bogdan Muntean

JUNIOR FRONT-END SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

/bogdan-muntean



@BogdanMuntean_



/bogdan-muntean-ro

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Over a year of intensive work in the tech field while working in parallel in another field, with a history of 10 years in which I had contact with the technological field. I learned essential languages and many other tools.

Passionate and determined, eager to learn new things every day. In the process of learning front end development with discipline and hunger for knowledge.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (Internship)

01/2022 - 05/2022

I learned from the front end development course advanced notions of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and about frameworks like React and Tailwind. As well as about Git, Github, SPA and Responsive Websites.

During the course I invested a lot of time with interest and conscientiousness. I did all the required and optional homework and projects and this thing had an important impact on the development skills of front-end side.

PHYSIOTHERAPIST (full-time) PHYSIOTHERAPIST (part-time) **HIGH-PERFORMANCE ATHLETE** 01/08/2022 - Current 10/11/2020 - 01/08/2022 2014-2021

Budo Gym Cluj-Napoca (Kyokushin Martial Arts)

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPMENT

Informal School of IT - Cluj-Napoca

01/2022 - 05/2022

CERTIFIED IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

"Lucian Blaga" High School - Cluj-Napoca

2017

High School - Section of Mathematics-Informatics Intensive Informatics 2013-2017 "Lucian Blaga" High School - Cluj-Napoca

Experienced with C++, C and about algorithms and problem-solving skills. Certificate of digital skills and professional skills in computer science.

COURSES

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

Responsive Web Design Certification

freeCodeCamp

Front-end Foundations

The Odin Project

I learned HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Command Line Basics, GitHub, GIT

Introduction to Computer Science

HarvardX CS50 (2020)

I learned C, HTML and CSS, the basics of machine learning, algorithms and structured data

ABCode Course

Language C